3vg58t1.com 2010-02-01

# adMarketplace.com - Performance Driven Pay Per Click Advertising

### Privacy Policy

adMarketplace, Inc.’s (“adMarketplace’s”) website serves two basic functions. First, it is a portal for information about adMarketplace products and services as well as online advertising generally. Second, it contains password-protected pages where adMarketplace partners can access partner-only materials. 

This Privacy Policy applies exclusively to information practices related to our website, [www.adMarketplace.com](http://www.admarketplace.com/). Although this website contains links to other websites, please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those, or any other sites. If you follow a link to another website you should carefully read their privacy policy. 

Personal Information Collected on this Website  
No personally-identifiable information is collected on this website from consumers that browse the website for information. 

The only personally-identifiable information collected on this website is gathered on our “contact us” pages, where fields are provided so that you can provide your name, email address and phone contact information. We collect this information so that we can respond to the comments that you send us via that form. 

adMarketplace is the sole owner of all information collected on this site. adMarketplace will not rent, sell or share any personally-identifiable information about you with third parties for any reason except when required to assist in resolving an issue you raise with us or required by law. 

We do not merge any of the personally-identifiable information collected via our contact form with other anonymous data collected on our website. 

Anonymous Information Collected on this Website  
We record anonymous data such as traffic logs, number of visits or clicks on a given page, pages viewed or links to our site. We use IP addresses and cookies for gathering website statistics. We also store IP addresses on our server in the event that our site should become corrupted and it becomes necessary to discover the cause of this corruption. 

We aggregate this anonymous data as part of managing, maintaining and reporting on use of our website. We may share this anonymous data with third parties for the limited purpose of reporting on use of our website, or to comply with applicable law. We do not rent, sell or share any anonymous data collected on this website with third parties for marketing purposes. 

None of this anonymous data is linked to personally-identifiable information and we make no attempt to link IP addresses to the individuals who visit this site. 

Cookies  
We use cookies on this website. 

Cookies are small chunks of data created by a web server, delivered through a web browser, and stored on your computer. They provide a means for websites that you visit to keep track of your online patterns and preferences, as well as identify you as a return visitor. Cookies make the personalization of your web experiences possible, so that you do not need to re-enter your information from scratch upon each visit to a given website. 

We serve a cookie from our website when partners log in to partner-only pages, so that they can navigate those pages on the site. A randomly-generated anonymous identifier is assigned to this Privacy Policy. 

No personally-identifiable information is collected by or linked to any of the cookies delivered on our site. 

You have the ability to manage the use of cookies on your computer using controls in your web-browser. To learn more about how to manage cookies, visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.com/>. 

Changes to Our Privacy Policy  
As our company and services evolve, this Privacy Policy may be revised to reflect those changes, where applicable. We therefore reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time, for any reason. Notice of such amendments will be posted as an updated Privacy Policy on this website, and an effective date will be indicated. Users are encouraged to check our site frequently to review the current Privacy Policy in effect. 

Questions?  
Please contact us with any questions about this website Privacy Policy.
